raisingchildren.net.au 2018-06-22

# Privacy statement for Raising Children Network | Raising Children Network

The Raising Children Network website provides information and services designed for parents, carers and professionals involved in rearing children.

This privacy statement applies to the raisingchildren.net.au website only (also accessed via [www.raisingchildren.net.au](http://www.raisingchildren.net.au/) and [m.raisingchildren.net.au](http://m.raisingchildren.net.au/)).

Your personal information is protected under the Privacy Act 1988. Raising Children Network collects personal and sensitive information if you choose to provide it, such as your email address and child's birth date. Your personal information will not be used other than for the purpose that you provide it without your consent.

Uses of personal information by Raising Children Network may include the provision of services; the development, maintenance and promotion of this website; evaluating Raising Children Network services, and conducting approved research. No information that personally identifies you is collected when you simply browse the site.

Raising Children Network will provide access to, and make corrections to, your personal information at your request, except in the circumstances set out in the Privacy Act 1988.  Personal information will not be disclosed or used for purposes other than the stated uses, functions and activities of Raising Children Network, unless the disclosure is required or authorised by law. 

Raising Children Network uses Google Analytics to help us understand how our people use this website. Non-identifying statistical information collected could include your server address, the top level domain name (such as .gov, .com, .edu), pages accessed or downloaded, search terms used, the date and time of site visits, your operating system (such as Windows) or browser system (such as Internet Explorer), and the site from which you entered the website or to which you exited. You can read more about how [Google uses your personal information](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en). You can also [opt-out of Google Analytics](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)  to prevent your data from being used by Google.

Raising Children Network may disclose non-identifying statistical information collected on this website to the Department of Social Services, to the Australian Council for Educational Research, and to organisations conducting approved research, such as universities and research centres.

If you have any questions about your privacy, please [email the Privacy Officer](mailto:privacy@raisingchildren.net.au?subject=Privacy%20enquiry) or contact:

**Raising Children Network Privacy Officer**   
Royal Children’s Hospital   
Flemington Road   
Parkville  Victoria  3052  
Australia
